POKER IN OCTOBER is a layered All Caps color font. 
 
Please note that this is primarily for headlines, logos posters in large size so there are no characters included that might be required in a body copy. 

This is a DEMO version of the Main font instance without the 3 other layers.

Free for personal use only

For all the 4 layers, a color SVG. font and commercial license

please visit my Creative Market store https://crmrkt.com/yR1KeR

The SVG font comes in the original color palette that you can change layers separately as you like in the otf font file that is a different font file and you need to install them both in case you like the default color font and the separate layers.

Feedback, questions, customisation and/or extra characters please contact me here or 
via rolandhuse.com

Background image (taken from Unsplash) credits:

Poker cards on table by Aditya Chinchure https://unsplash.com/@adityachinchure/portfolio

Have A Great Day by Bailey Zindel https://unsplash.com/@baileyzindel

Wild&Free by Eberhard Grossgasteiger https://unsplash.com/@eberhardgross/portfolio

* * *

You may not

sell these fonts or claim them as your own.

edit or rename these fonts.

redistribute these fonts.

* * *

Find more of my works on instagram @rolandhusedesign

Thank you and hope you like this font!

Have a great day and good luck with your work,

Roland